

PROFILE

Versatile, result-driven professional with experience developing web applications. Equipped with problem solving and analytical skills, fast learning curve and able to adapt to continuous evolving industrial trends. A dedicated professional with the drive and skill-set to excel in a fast-paced industry, understands targets and enhances the profitability of the company.

CONTACT

PHONE:

8178427237, 9643097626

WEBSITE:

https://abhishekbindra.netlify.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhishekbindra-67b710106/

EMAIL:

abhishek.bindra.ab@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Playing Guitar Listening Music Watching TV Series

EXTRA CURRICULAR

Organized tech events in college fest CORONA.

Member of Computer Society of India. Part of Campus Ambassador Programme.

Won Interschool Programming Competition in class 12th.

ABHISHEK BINDRA

Full Stack Developer

EDUCATION

B. Tech (Computer Science Engineering)

Bhagwan Parshuram Institute of Technology 2017 – 2021

Mount Abu Public School

AISSCE (2017) with 94.2% SSC (2015) with 10 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Skodun – Software Developer

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

- -- A smart web-based platform to conduct hassle free paperless audits.
- -- Automated report generation facility along with analytics that helps track business progress.

Beaumir – Full Stack Developer

Jun 2019 - July 2019

- -- Developed UI Mirror Interface for direct customer interaction.
- -- Owner & Manager Portal for reports, billing & customized configs.
- -- Developed Vizmae: A portal to manage visiting cards hassle free

idealVillage – Full Stack Web Developer

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

- -- Creating & Maintaining server-side scripts & database using PHP.
- -- Worked on Job Portal engaging different roles such as Student, Admin, Staff, and Employer and on Website Builder handling Templates, User Navigation, Payment Gateway Integration, and FTP Deployment.

SKILLS

